ARTSIOM SAUCHUK



JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPER

WWW.A-SAUCHUK.VERCEL.APP



ABOUT ME

I'm a JavaScript (FE/BE) Developer with more than 3 years of experience in developing user interfaces, testing, debugging. Have a proven ability to collaborate effectively with senior developers. Enjoy working with team members to ensure workloads are effectively redirected to bottlenecks. Mentor of the students in The Rolling Scopes School. Dedicated and hard working with internal drive to succeed.



CONTACT

Address:

Minsk, BELARUS

Mobile:

+375 29 791 58 36

Telegram:

t.me/hansolo_666

Email:

savchuk799@gmail.com



LANGUAGES

RUSSIAN — NATIVE

ENGLISH — B1



SKILLS

HTML/CSS Jest

JavaScript Webpack

React.JS

Git

Redux Node.js

TypeScript PostgeSQL

Json/REST API MongoDB

JIRA Svelte.JS



EXPERIENCES

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

2023 - NOW

- Development and maintainment of web applications

(React.js, Svelte.js, Vue.js, Node.js).
- Implementation of Motion Design animations in CSS

- Responsive design Implementation.

- Collaboration with designers and PMs (Figma, Zeplin).

- Performance optimization and debugging.

FRONTEND DEVELOPER EPAM SYSTEMS

2022 - 2023 - Development of new user-facing features, optimisation.

- E2E Testing.

AIBY, INC.

- Participation in daily meetings and scrum sessions.

POWER ENGINEER OOO ELECTROSCHIT-SERVICE

2018 - 2021 - Development of electrical circuits.

Project management. Personnel management.

POWER ENGINEER OOO ARTKA-ENERGO

2017 - 2018 - Electrical installation works.

- Permission obtainment in state structures.



2012 - 2017

EDUCATION

EPAM SYSTEMS NODE JS WEB TRAINIG

2022 JS Lab NODE.JS Short Track Course

THE ROLLING SCOPES CERTIFICATE OF WEB TRAINIG

REACT 2021Q3 (JAVASCRIPT)

2021 LINK: https://app.rs.school/certificate/ith7gxcc

THE ROLLING SCOPES CERTIFICATE OF WEB TRAINIG

JAVASCRIPT/FRONT-END 2021Q1 (JAVASCRIPT)

2021 LINK: https://app.rs.school/certificate/2faovg51

BELARUSSIAN NATIONAL BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN POWER ENGINEERING

TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY
Faculty: Power Engineering

Speciality: Electric Power Systems and Grids